fotoglif.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Fotoglif

**Fotoglif Privacy Policy**

Fotoglif is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit any of our websites (“Fotoglif Sites”) or while using our electronic services or applications (“Services”). In this policy we explain how and why we collect your information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.

From time to time, we add or change functions, features or products related to the Fotoglif Sites or add or change Services. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy which we may change at any time with or without advance notice.

As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments.  Using the Fotoglif Sites or Service after a change in the Privacy Policy has been made constitutes your consent to the changed terms or practices.

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to [support@fotoglif.com](mailto:support@fotoglif.com).

**_Your acceptance of these Privacy Statement terms_**

By using any of the Fotoglif Sites or Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

**_What data do we collect and how do we use it?_**

  * **Registration**

In order make full use of the Fotoglif Sites to license, download or embed content (“Content”), you must register for a user account (“User Account”). You must provide us the following information to create an account: your name, email address, website, audience size, country, and password. You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences. In addition, when you order certain goods or services from the Fotoglif Sites, we will need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date.

You will be asked to create a password and to confirm that password. Like other passwords, you should choose one that is known only by you. You acknowledge that this information is personal to you, and by creating an account on Fotoglif, you allow others, including Fotoglif, to identify you.

  * **Additional Information**

Once you have a User Account, you may provide additional information including among other things your job title and address. Providing additional information about yourself beyond what is minimally required at registration is at your discretion. Any information you provide at registration or in the My Account section may be used by Fotoglif as described in the End User Agreement and this Privacy Policy, including for the purpose of serving advertisements through the Services. If you decide not to provide us with certain information, you may be entitled to receive the full benefits of the Fotoglif Sites and Services.

  * **Customer Service**

We may collect information through the Fotoglif Sites in order to accurately categorize and respond to customer inquiries and investigate breaches of our terms among other things.

  * **Site and Service Usage**

Fotoglif collects and processes information about you in order to:

  * Identify you each time you visit a Fotoglif Site or wish to have a Service provided
  * Process orders or registration applications submitted by you
  * Improve our Services and Fotoglif Sites
  * Customize your experience on the Fotoglif Sites and Services
  * Provide advertisements that we think are relevant to you and which support any specific requests for information you may make through keyword searches
  * Provide advertisements that accompany the Content that we think are relevant to you or your website or application users
  * Carry out research on the demographics, interests and behavior of all of our customers on an anonymous basis
  * Send you information we think you may find useful, including information about new Fotoglif products and Services.

You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences. In addition, when you order certain goods or services from the Fotoglif Sites, we will need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date.

You are under no obligation to provide this information, but if you don’t then we may not be able to provide you with certain services or personalize your experience and tailor our Services for you.

  * **Log files, IP Address and Device Information**

When you visit a Fotoglif Site, or use a Fotoglif application, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet), which is automatically recognized by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer the Fotoglif Sites and Services and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use.

  * **Non-personal information**

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of Internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to the Fotoglif Sites. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on the Fotoglif Sites. We may from time to time supply the owners or operators of third party websites from which it is possible to link to the Fotoglif Sites with information relating to the number of users linking to the Fotoglif Sites from their sites. You cannot be identified from this information.

  * **Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Fotoglif Sites if you do so.

Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web.  Although they do identify a user’s computer, cookies do not personally identify customers or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.

We use cookies for the following reasons:

  * To identify who you are and to access your account information
  * To estimate our audience size and patterns
  * To ensure that you are not asked to register twice
  * To control how often visitors see similar ads
  * To track preferences and to improve and update the Fotoglif Sites

  * **Use of Personal Information**

Fotoglif will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party suppliers who provide services on our behalf.

Fotoglif may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our website visitors and customers of our services in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

Fotoglif may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Fotoglif, its parent company or investors or visitors to the Fotoglif Sites and customers of our Services.

The Fotoglif Sites contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. Fotoglif is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

We will only sell or rent your personal information to a third party either as part of a sale of the assets of the company or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

  * **Information about products and services**

As described in the End User Agreement, we will communicate with you through email or through other means available through the service, including mobile text messages. We may send you emails that help inform you of new content available that might be of interest to you. We will also send you messages relating to the functioning of the Services or new features or content available to you. We may also send you messages with promotional information directly or on behalf of our partners, unless you have opted out of receiving promotional information.

You can also opt-out of receiving promotional emails by sending a request to [support@Fotoglif.com](mailto:support@Fotoglif.com) or directly by unsubscribing at the bottom of any email we may send you. If we send communications to you via your mobile phone service, you understand you will pay any associated service fees for receipt of messages on your mobile device (including text messaging charges).

  * **Security**

Fotoglif places a great importance on the security of all information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized personnel have access to user information. With regard to the Fotoglif Sites, we use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

**Comments**

Please e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about our Privacy Policy to [support@fotoglif.com](mailto:support@fotoglif.com)  
or write to us at:

Fotoglif  
219 Dufferin Street  
Toronto, Ontario M6K 1Y9  
Canada
